A Guide to the John D. Chapla Papers, 1972-2013
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Alexander Welch Reynolds Research Files., Extent: 8 boxes. (Box 39-46)
  - National Archives - Solicitor of the Treasury - Closed Cases (RG206). (Box 44, Folder 7-8)
  - New Mexico Historical Review. (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - New Mexico in 1850: A Military View by Col. George Archibald McCall. (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - New Mexico's Quest for Statehood, 1846-1912 by Robert W. Larson. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - The New York Times. (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - North Carolina Troops, 1861-1865 (58th and 60th Regiments). (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - ' "Notorious as the Noonday Sun" - Capt. Alexander Welch Reynolds and the New Mexico Territory, 1849-1859 - An Investigation' New Mexico Historical Review (October 2000). (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - ' "Oh what a turbill Affair" - Alexander W. Reynolds and His North Carolina-Virginia Brigade at Missionary Ridge, Tennessee, November 25, 1863' The North Carolina Historical Review (July 2000). (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Philadelphia City Directory. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Philadelphia Inquirer. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Reynolds, Alexander W. - U.S. Army Service Record, 1838-1861. (Box 45, Folder 4-6)
  - Reynolds Marker - St. James the Less Church, Philadelphia. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Reynolds Photographs - U.S. Army Military History Institute. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Senate and House Documents. (Box 45, Folder 9-10)
  - Soldier of Misfortune: Alexander Welch Reynolds of the United States, Confederate, and Egyptian Armies (Greenbrier Historical Society), 2001. (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Sources. (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - The South Reports the Civil War by J. Cutler Andrews. (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - United States Military Academy - Staff and Faculty. (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Van Dyke, James C. and Reynolds, Alexander W. - Historical Society of Pennsylvania. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Weightman, Richard H. - House Speech, 15 March 1852. (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Weightman, Richard H. - West Point. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - West Virginia University. (Box 46, Folder 5-7)